http://www.mevorahlaw.com/privacy-policy

Menu
HomeAbout UsAttorneys Steven H. Mevorah Steven H. Mevorah: Case SuccessesSteven H. Mevorah: Client TestimonialsBradley C. Giglio Brad C. Giglio: TestimonialsPaul H. Millewich Paul H. Millewich: Case SuccessesPaul H. Millewich: Client TestimonialsJason G. Shore Jason G. Shore: Case SuccessesJason G. Shore: Client TestimonialsRichard F. Doerr (Ret.) Richard F. Doerr: Case SuccessesRichard F. Doerr: Client TestimonialsMatthew B. Sperry Matthew B. Sperry: Case SuccessesMatthew B. Sperry: Client TestimonialsCharles N. Ogan Charles N. Ogan: Client TestimonialsRichard L. ElsligerFrancis T. CermakAlyana J. AbellarPractice Areas Divorce Alimony and Maintenance Unallocated MaintenanceChild Support College ExpensesSpecial Needs Children and DivorceParental Responsibility (Custody) Sole Custody vs. Joint CustodyParenting Plans and VisitationChild RelocationProperty and Asset Division Retirement, 401k Accounts and PensionsDebt Division Bankruptcy in DivorcePost Decree ModificationsPost Decree Enforcement and Contempt HearingsDissolution of Arranged MarriagesTax Consequences and DivorceUncontested DivorceDivorce Involving Mental Health Issues or AddictionsDivorce and the Stay-at-Home ParentDivorce FAQsFamily Law AdoptionParentage (Paternity)Child SupportAllocation of Parental Responsibility (Child Custody)Parenting Time (Visitation)Grandparents Visitation RightsGuardianshipPrenuptial and Postnuptial AgreementsDomestic Violence Orders of ProtectionLegal SeparationAlternative Dispute ResolutionSuccess Stories Workers' Compensation Success StoriesTestimonialsBlogMedia
Press ReleasesVideo GalleryContact Lombard OfficeBloomingdale OfficeChicago OfficeNaperville OfficePress ReleasesNaperville, IL Divorce Lawyers
LOMBARD630-932-9100
BLOOMINGDALE630-529-4761
CHICAGO630-932-9100
NAPERVILLE630-420-1000
Contact Us Today
Back to Top
4 Convenient Locations
LOMBARD
Phone: 630-420-1000
Privacy PolicyThis statement applies to the online collection of personal information via websites operated by and applications offered by Mevorah Law Offices LLC. Details of the Privacy Statement follow immediately below.What personal information is collected and how is that information used?We collect information about our users in three ways: directly from the user (such as when ordering a product, registering an account or signing up for a newsletter), from our Web server logs, and through cookies.We use the information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you.We do not share any of the information you provide with others, unless we say so in this Privacy Statement, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.How is my personal information protected?We have implemented certain appropriate security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.However, please note that we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures.Also, please note that we may store and process your personal information in systems located outside of your home country. Regardless of where these activities occur, we take appropriate steps to ensure that your information is protected consistent with the principles set forth under this Privacy Statement.Who has access to the personal information?We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other customer data to others, and we will not make your personal information available to any unaffiliated parties, except our approved agents and contractors, or as otherwise described in this Privacy Statement.We rely on some of our affiliates for support of the products and services we offer, and we share some of our back-office functions with other companies. Our affiliates are all required to preserve the confidentiality of any personal information they may access.We will not disclose any personal information or information about your usage of our websites to unaffiliated third parties, except as necessary to service the account, to enforce the terms of use, to meet our obligations to content and technology providers, or as required by law.How may I correct, amend or delete my personal information, or update my preferences?You may cancel your registration or update your preferences at any time simply by contacting us.If you do not want to receive information about our products or services, please contact us.If you have any additional questions or concerns related to this statement and/or our practices, please contact us at:Mevorah Law Offices LLC900 East Roosevelt RoadLombard, IL 60148Phone: 630-932-9100
Download Our Brochure
Let us start helping you with a FREE initial consultation.
One Stop For All Your Legal Needs
Whether you are going through a divorce, injured in an accident, need to file a workers' compensation claim, charged with a crime, immigrating to the United States, or need to file for bankruptcy, Mevorah Law Offices LLC can help. Our trial lawyers have over 40 years of experience helping clients throughout Northern Illinois from four offices in Lombard, Bloomindale, Naperville, St. Charles, and Chicago.
Steven Mevorah has assembled experienced attorneys under one roof so that his clients need not search for a new attorney each time they need help.
Mr. Mevorah has also established a wide network of additional attorneys so that his clients merely need to stop by Mevorah Law Offices LLC to find the attorney they need.
Client Focused Representation
Our practice is focused on meeting your needs with flexible hours and locations to serve you:
Free initial consultations
Saturday and evening appointments available
Home and hospital visits if your injuries prevent you from traveling
